presorium.com 2006-05-04

# Presorium Software Privacy Statement

### Presorium Software Privacy Statement

**Presorium Software Pty. Ltd. ("Presorium") takes your privacy very seriously.  
Our policy regarding the handling of personal information is as follows :**

**Correspondence**

Presorium reserves the right to publish all correspondence, where "Correspondence" means communication, written or verbal, sent to or from Presorium by electronic or other means and authored by an individual, whether a private user, company representative or otherwise. 

If you do not wish for your correspondence to be published, please label it appropriately. In most cases Presorium will not publish any material without the express consent of the author. 

Presorium does not provide or claim to provide secure storage for correspondence received. Please do not send us any sensitive or private information unless it is absolutely necessary. 

**Mailing Lists**

All addresses supplied to Presorium for mailing list subscriptions are used solely for the mailing list, for instance to notify you of new software releases, updates and the like. For your convenience, each announcement contains instructions on how to be removed from all future mailings. We do not disclose your e-mail address to any third parties. 

**User Registration**

It is very important for Presorium to keep accurate registration records. For registration, we collect information such as name and e-mail address. This data is used only to identify you in order to give you the full benefits of registration including technical support, upgrade eligibility and replacement in case of lost registration. We do not disclose this information to any third parties and it is stored securely.

**HTTP Cookies**

HTTP cookies are not being used at this website.

**Formalities Aside...**

At the risk of sounding off-hand, we at presorium have no interest in anyone's personal information whatsoever! We do not want to know anything about anyone unless it is essential in order for us to provide as good a service as possible. We find the concepts of "spyware" and intruding on personal space abhorrent. We respect people's privacy and have a low opinion of those who don't.  
These are the very reasons why we made Frontgate MX. 

This is the extent of our collection and use of personal information. Further enquiries should be directed to enquiries at presorium dot com (email)

This statement effective from the **16th of July, 2003**.
